ILGWU. James Lipsig papers, 5780/082
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. Legal appeals and cases
  - Berde, Eugen. Board of Immigration Appeals and Naturalization [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1955 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Berde, Eugen. Board of Immigration Appeals and Naturalization [folder 1 of 3], 1953-1955 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Berde, Eugen. Board of Immigration Appeals and Naturalization [folder 2 of 3], 1954 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Berde, Eugen. Board of Immigration Appeals and Naturalization [folder 3 of 3], 1952-1953 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Berde, Eugen. Mortgage Loan Materials, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Berde, Eugen. Tax Liability Materials, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Berde, Eugen. Visa Application Materials [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Berde, Eugen. Visa Application Materials [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Dinerstein v. Union Health Care Center, 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Gaffney v. Tomaine, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Grobin v. Grobin, 1947-1948 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Kovacs v. Union Health Care Center, 1946-1947 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Lipsig v. Schwalm's Express Company, Inc. American Arbitration Association Procedure, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lipsig v. Schwalm's Express Company. Legal Notes, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Lipsig v. Schwalm's Express Company. Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Lipsig v. Schwalm's Express Company. Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Lurye Film Contracts [folder 1 of 2], 1950 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Lurye Film Contracts [folder 2 of 2], 1950 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lurye Trust Fund Materials, 1949-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Montana, Vanni and Helene [folder 1 of 2], 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Montana, Vanni and Helene [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1962 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Price v. Dubinsky [folder 1 of 6], 1948-1961 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Price v. Dubinsky [folder 2 of 6], 1960 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Price v. Dubinsky [folder 3 of 6], 1948-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Price v. Dubinksy [folder 4 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Price v. Dubinsky [folder 5 of 6], 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Price v. Dubinsky [folder 6 of 6], 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Tobias v. Tobias [folder 1 of 3], 1946 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Tobias v. Tobias [folder 2 of 3], 1946 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Tobias v. Tobias [folder 3 of 3], 1946 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Upper South Department. Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Upper South Department. Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Wentworth Manufacturing Company. Southwest Region [folder 1 of 4], 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Wentworth Manufacturing Company. Southwest Region [folder 2 of 4], 1954-1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Wentworth Manufacturing Company. Southwest Region [folder 3 of 4], 1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Wentworth Manufacturing Company. Southwest Region [folder 4 of 4], 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)